(Sheldon:)Lucky Baldwin's.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I've heard
of that place.
(Sheldon:)Isn't that Pasadena's
favorite Irish watering hole?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Did you meet
(Sheldon:)anyone interesting there,
(Sheldon:)perhaps a promiscuous,
redheaded barmaid?
(Leonard:)As a matter of fact...
I-I-I-I-I can't, I can't,
(Leonard:)I can't do it.
(Sheldon:)Sure you can, you're doing
fine, it's very believable.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, Raj,
but the truth is,
(Leonard:)I was with Priya
last night.
(Sheldon:)Don't listen to him.
He's still light-headed
from all the Irish whiskey
(Sheldon:)and pickled eggs
in his system.
(Howard:)What were you doing
with Priya?
(Sheldon:)I believe they engaged
in coitus,
(Sheldon:)but more
importantly,
(Sheldon:)if Leonard had not abandoned
his story,
(Sheldon:)would you have found it
plausible?
You slept with my sister?!
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Howard:)How could you?
We had a pact.
(Raj:)Excuse me, I think
"How could you? She's my sister"
(Raj:)takes precedence over
a five-year-old pinky swear.
(Sheldon:)May I point out,
(Sheldon:)in a parallel universe,
your friends are saying
"Maggie McGarry--
she sounds lovely."